Rush family papers LCP.Rush
Library Company of Philadelphia
- Series II. James Rush papers
  - Subseries IV. Correspondence, circa 1813-1869
    - C. Dr. James and Mrs. Phoebe Rush's invitations, acceptances and rejections of social events, [Yi2 7407 -Yi2 7413]
      - Bridges, Mary [invitation to the funeral of], undated (Box 7, Folder 66)
      - Brinton, Mrs. and Miss, undated (Box 7, Folder 67)
      - Broek, Frederic van den [wedding invitations], undated (Box 7, Folder 68)
      - Brooke, Mr. and Mrs. C. Wallace, undated (Box 7, Folder 69)
      - Brown, Mrs., undated (Box 7, Folder 70)
      - Brown, Mr., Mrs. J.A., and Miss, undated (Box 7, Folder 71)
      - Bown, J.A., undated (Box 7, Folder 72)
      - Brown, Dr., undated (Box 7, Folder 73)
      - Browne, 1836 March 15 (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Bullock, Miss Sophia [invitation to funeral of], 1843 December 18 (Box 7, Folder 75)
      - Burd, Mr. and Mrs. E.S. and Miss Elizabeth, 1835, undated (Box 7, Folder 76)
      - Butler, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Byrne, Lieutenant, undated (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Cadwalader, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Cadwalader, H., undated (Box 7, Folder 80)
      - Cadwalader, General Thomas [invitation to funeral of], 1841 October 26 (Box 7, Folder 81)
      - Cadwalader, Thomas C. [invitation to funeral of], 1844 January 20 (Box 7, Folder 82)
      - Cadwalader, J.C., undated (Box 7, Folder 83)
      - Cadwalader, Mr. and Mrs. George, undated (Box 7, Folder 84)
      - Cadwalader, Mr. and Mrs. John, undated (Box 7, Folder 85)
      - Camac, Mr., 1834-1838, undated (Box 7, Folder 86)
      - Campbell, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 7, Folder 87)
      - Campbell, St. George J., undated (Box 7, Folder 88)
      - Carleton, Henry [invitation to funeral of], undated (Box 7, Folder 89)
      - Carman, Mary Anna [invitation to funeral of], 1841 February 18 (Box 7, Folder 90)
      - Carroll, Mrs., undated (Box 7, Folder 91)
      - Carstensen, George, undated (Box 7, Folder 92)
      - Catron, Judge and Mrs., undated (Box 7, Folder 93)
      - Carylin, Earnest, undated (Box 7, Folder 94)
      - Carwin, Miss [invitation to funeral of], undated (Box 7, Folder 95)
      - Chacon, Chavalier DonPablo, Consul General of Spain for the United States [invitation to funeral of], 1844, August 29 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Chancellor, Mr., undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Chapron, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Chew, B., undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Chew, Maria [invitation to funeral of], 1840 March 28 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Chew, Samuel [invitation to funeral of], 1841 August 23 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Chew, W.W., 1832 March 16 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Chew, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Chotard, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Chrystler, Mrs. Lydia J. [invitation to funeral of], 1841 October 6 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Church, Mr., undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Clapier, Mr., Mrs. And Miss, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Clay, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Coleman, Mr., Mrs. and Miss, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Coles, Mr. and Mrs. Edward, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Colhoun, Dr. S., 1835-1838 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Colman, James, 1849 February 12 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Combe, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Connell, Mr., 1837 March 20 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - Cooke, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - Cooper, Caroline Fenimore, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - Corbin, Mr., undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - Cowell, John V., undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
      - Cox, Mr. and Mrs. Markoe, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
      - Cox, Mr. and Mrs. J., undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
      - Cox, John W., undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
      - Coxe, C.S., undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - Coxe, D.W., 1835, undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
      - Coxe, E.S., undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
      - Coxe, J., undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
      - Coxe, Mrs. and Miss, undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
      - Craig, J., undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
      - Craig, J.C., undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
      - Craig, J.J., undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
      - Craig, Mr., undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
      - Cramond, H., undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
      - Cristina Carolina, Queen of the Two Sicilies [invitation to the funeral of], 1836 April 8 (Box 8, Folder 37)
      - Croskey, Mrs., undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
      - Croskey, Mr. H., undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
      - Crothers, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
      - Dale, Mr. and Mrs. Edward C., undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
      - Dallas, A.G., 1819 January 5 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - Dallas, G.M., 1840, undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
      - Darrach, Mrs. Margaretta [invitation to funeral of], 1841 July 17 (Box 8, Folder 44)
      - Davis, Mr., Mrs. and Miss, undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
      - D'Avrainville, Mr., undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
      - D'Avrainville, Alexander [invitation to funeral of], 1836 December 24 (Box 8, Folder 47)
      - Dehon, Mr., 1836 April 29 (Box 8, Folder 48)
      - Delaney, Miss, undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
      - DePethe, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 8, Folder 50)
      - Desilver, Robert [invitation to funeral of], 1837 September 15 (Box 8, Folder 51)
      - De Hauteville, Mrs., undated (Box 8, Folder 52)
      - Dickey, J.G., undated (Box 8, Folder 53)
      - Dickson, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 8, Folder 54)
      - Dorsey, Miss, undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
      - Drayton, William, 1834-1843 (Box 8, Folder 56)
      - Drouin, F., 1834 February 4 (Box 8, Folder 57)
      - Dubois, Mr., undated (Box 8, Folder 58)
      - Duncan, Dr. and Mrs., 1809, undated (Box 8, Folder 59)
      - Dundas, David, 1845 July 6 (Box 8, Folder 60)
      - Dunlap, J., 1839 December 30 (Box 8, Folder 61)
      - Dunn, N., 1837-1840, undated (Box 8, Folder 62)
      - Du Ponceau, Mr., 1834-1841, undated (Box 8, Folder 63)
      - Du Ponceau, Peter [invitation to the funeral of], 1844 April 2 (Box 8, Folder 64)
      - Elliot, C., undated (Box 8, Folder 65)
      - Elwyn, A.S., undated (Box 8, Folder 66)
      - Elwyn, Alfred, undated (Box 8, Folder 67)
      - Elwyn, Mr. Langden, undated (Box 8, Folder 68)
      - Emlen, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 8, Folder 69)
      - Emory, R., 1831 April 26 (Box 8, Folder 70)
      - Etting, B., undated (Box 8, Folder 71)
      - Evans, Mrs., undated (Box 8, Folder 72-73)
      - Eyre, Mr. and Miss, undated (Box 8, Folder 74)
      - Farrar, E., undated (Box 8, Folder 75)
      - Ferguson, Mrs. Jane [invitation to the funeral of], 1840 March 4 (Box 8, Folder 76)
      - Finney, Mrs., undated (Box 8, Folder 77)
      - [Figaniere], Madame C. de, undated (Box 8, Folder 78)
      - Fisher, Mr. and Mrs. C.H., undated (Box 8, Folder 79)
      - Fisher, Mr. and Mrs. E.P., undated (Box 8, Folder 80)
      - Fisher, G., [1825] July 13 (Box 8, Folder 81)
      - Fisher, James C. [invitation to the funeral of], 1840 October 17 (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Fisher, J. C., undated (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - Fisher, J. Francis, undated (Box 8, Folder 84)
      - Fisher, Mrs. S.W, undated (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Fisher, William, undated (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Florance, Mrs. and Misses, undated (Box 8, Folder 87)
      - Foulhouze, Mr., undated (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Fox, Mrs. C.P., undated (Box 8, Folder 89)
      - Fox, Miss, undated (Box 8, Folder 90)
      - Francis, Charles, Jr. [invitation to the funeral of], 1835 November 28 (Box 8, Folder 91)
      - Francis, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 8, Folder 92)
      - Francis, Alfred, undated (Box 8, Folder 93)
      - Francis, Mrs. W., undated (Box 8, Folder 94)
      - Fullerton, Alexander [invitation to the funeral of], 1840 August 1 (Box 8, Folder 95)
      - Fullerton, Alexander, Jr., undated (Box 8, Folder 96)
      - Fullerton, Mr. and Mrs., 1836-1862, undated (Box 8, Folder 97)
      - Furness, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 8, Folder 98)
      - Gadsden, Miss, undated (Box 8, Folder 99)
      - Ganon, J. H., 1843 August 15 (Box 8, Folder 100)
      - Gano, Mrs. Mary [invitation to the funeral of], 1838 May 7 (Box 8, Folder 101)
      - Garesche, Mr. and Miss, undated (Box 8, Folder 102)
      - Garreau, A, undated (Box 8, Folder 103)
      - Gibson, Dr. and Mrs. C.B., undated (Box 8, Folder 104)
      - Gibson, Judge [James], undated (Box 8, Folder 105)
      - Gillaspy, M. Anna, undated (Box 8, Folder 106)
      - Gilpin, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 8, Folder 107)
      - Grant, Mrs., undated (Box 8, Folder 108)
      - Gratz, Rebecca, undated (Box 8, Folder 109)
      - Greene, William [invitation to the funeral of], annotated, 1839 October 31 (Box 8, Folder 110)
      - Greeland, Mr., Mrs. and Miss, undated (Box 8, Folder 111)
      - Greeland, Aurora, undated (Box 8, Folder 112)
      - Griffith, Dr. and Mrs. R.E., undated (Box 8, Folder 113)
      - Gross, Dr. and Mrs., undated (Box 8, Folder 114)
      - Guthrie, Anne S., undated (Box 8, Folder 115)
      - Haldane, [W.], undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Hall, S.J., undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Hamilton, Mary [invitation to funeral of], 1849 April (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Hamilton, Miss [Mary], 1838, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Hare, Dr. and Mrs. Robert, 1832, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Hare, Mrs. C.W. and Miss C.E., undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Harris, Mrs. Thomas [invitation to the funeral of], 1834 July 29 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Harris, Dr. and Mrs. Thomas, 1840, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Harris, William A., undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Harrison, George, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Harrison, Sophia, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Hawkins, William, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Hazard, Mary, 1836-1867, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Hazlehurst, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Henderson, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - Henry, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - Hersant, Mr. and Mrs., 1838-1839, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Hewson, Dr. and Miss Baker, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - Hodgson, Mrs., undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Hogg, Mrs., undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - Hoope, H. [or Hooke?], undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Hoope, Mrs. and Miss, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
      - Hope, Dr., undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - Hopkinson, A., undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - Hopkinson, Mr. and Mrs. F., 1840, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
      - Hopkinson, James, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
      - Howland, G.G., undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
      - Huger, F.K., 1837 September 19 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      - Hunt, Mrs. and Miss, undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
      - Hunter, Mr. and Mrs., 1843-1845 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      - Hupfeld, C.F., undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
      - Hutchinson, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
      - Ingersoll, Mr., Mrs. and Misses, undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
      - Ingersoll, C.A., undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
      - Ingersoll, Mr. and Mrs. Charles J., undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
      - Ingersoll, J.R., 1837, undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
      - Ingersoll, M.W., undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
      - Ingersoll, Susan C., undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
      - Ingraham, Mr. and Mrs. Alfred, undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
      - Ingraham, Mr., Mrs. and Miss, undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
      - Iredell, James, undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
      - Izard, R. F., undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
      - Izard, Misses, undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
      - Jackson, Mr., Mrs. and Miss, undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
      - Jackson, William, undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
      - James, Dr. Thomas [invitation to the funeral of], 1835 July 6 (Box 9, Folder 46)
      - Jenkins, Miss, undated (Box 9, Folder 47)
      - Jewett, Mrs., undated (Box 9, Folder 48)
      - Jones, Mr., 1844 October 25 (Box 9, Folder 49)
      - Jones, Mrs. Eliza, undated (Box 9, Folder 50)
      - Jones, Judge and Mrs., undated (Box 9, Folder 51)
      - Keating, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 9, Folder 52)
      - Keith, Washington and William, undated (Box 9, Folder 53)
      - Kemble, George [invitation to the funeral of], 1838 January 16 (Box 9, Folder 54)
      - Kennedy, A.E., undated (Box 9, Folder 55)
      - Keppele, Mrs., undated (Box 9, Folder 56)
      - Kershaw, Mr., undated (Box 9, Folder 57)
      - Knowles, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 9, Folder 58)
      - Kortright, Mr., undated (Box 9, Folder 59)
      - Kuhn, Miss E., undated (Box 9, Folder 60)
      - Kuhn, Dr. and Mrs. H., undated (Box 9, Folder 61)
      - Kuhn, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 9, Folder 62)
      - Hawkins, Dr. Edwin R. regarding death of Mr. Mary Lamb, 1868 July 22 (Box 9, Folder 63)
      - Lambert, J.R., undated (Box 9, Folder 64)
      - Lang, Dr., 1844 October 24 (Box 9, Folder 65)
      - Langdale, Lord and Lady (Bickersteth, Henry), undated (Box 9, Folder 66)
      - Landsdowne, Lord (Henry Petty-Fitzmaurice), undated (Box 9, Folder 67)
      - Lardner, Mr. and Mrs. James, undated (Box 9, Folder 68)
      - Lardner, Miss, undated (Box 9, Folder 69)
      - Latimer, Mr. and Mrs. J.R., 1836-1838, undated (Box 9, Folder 70)
      - Laussat, Antony [invitation to the funeral of], 1833 October 29 (Box 9, Folder 71)
      - Laussat, Mrs. and Miss, undated (Box 9, Folder 72)
      - Lee, Mrs., undated (Box 9, Folder 73)
      - LeGreen, Mr., undated (Box 9, Folder 74)
      - Lenox, Mrs. [invitation to the funeral of], 1834 August 25 (Box 9, Folder 75)
      - Levy, Mrs., undated (Box 9, Folder 76)
      - Lewis, Lawrence, undated (Box 9, Folder 77)
      - Lewis, Miss M.S., undated (Box 9, Folder 78)
      - Lewis, Mrs. Rachel [invitation to the funeral of], 1836 March 17 (Box 9, Folder 79)
      - Lewis, Mrs. R.M., undated (Box 9, Folder 80)
      - Lewis, S.N., undated (Box 9, Folder 81)
      - Lewis, William D., undated (Box 9, Folder 82)
      - Lewis, Mr., Mrs. and Misses, undated (Box 9, Folder 83)
      - Lippincott, William, undated (Box 9, Folder 84)
      - Livingston, Mr., undated (Box 9, Folder 85)
      - Livingston, Mr. and Mrs. Carroll, undated (Box 9, Folder 86)
      - Logan, Mr., Mrs. and Miss, undated (Box 9, Folder 87)
      - Lord, Mrs., undated (Box 9, Folder 88)
      - Lyman, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 9, Folder 89)
      - Macalester, Charles and Eliza Ann, undated (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Macalester, Mrs. Eliza Ann [invitation to the funeral of], 1835 August 31 (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - McCall, G.C., undated (Box 9, Folder 92)
      - McCall, P., undated (Box 9, Folder 93)
      - McCall, Robert, undated (Box 9, Folder 94)
      - McClellan, E.S., undated (Box 9, Folder 95)
      - McEuen, Mrs., undated (Box 9, Folder 96)
      - McIlvaine, Mr. and Miss, undated (Box 9, Folder 97)
      - McKean, P.E.W., undated (Box 9, Folder 98)
      - McKenney, Mrs. Editha [obituary], undated (Box 9, Folder 99)
      - McMinn, William [invitation to the funeral of], 1840 March 26 (Box 9, Folder 100)
      - McMurtrie, Mr. and Mrs. R.M. and Miss, undated (Box 9, Folder 101)
      - Macpherson, Miss, undated (Box 9, Folder 102)
      - Mactier, Mr., undated (Box 9, Folder 103)
      - Magee, Mrs., undated (Box 9, Folder 104)
      - Mailliard, Monsieurs L. and A., 1839 February 28 (Box 9, Folder 105)
      - [Markol], Mr. and Mrs. James and Miss, undated (Box 9, Folder 106)
      - Marryat, Charlotte, undated (Box 9, Folder 107)
      - Marshall, Miss, undated (Box 9, Folder 108)
      - Martin, Mr., 1845 July 12 (Box 9, Folder 109)
      - Meade, G., undated (Box 9, Folder 110)
      - Mease, Dr., undated (Box 9, Folder 111)
      - Mease, Isabelle, undated (Box 9, Folder 112)
      - Meredith, William [invitation to the funeral of], 1844 September 28 (Box 9, Folder 113)
      - Meredith, Mr., Mrs. and the Misses, undated (Box 9, Folder 114)
      - Merino, Augustus, undated (Box 9, Folder 115)
      - Middleton, Mrs. and Misses, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Mifflin, Mrs. Charles, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Miller, A., 1810 June 19 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Miller, Clements S., 1841, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Miller, G., 1810 July 19 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Miller, John, 1845 June 6 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Miller, Juliana, 1843 January 18 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Miller, Colonel, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Milligan, Miss and Miss Blight, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Milroy, Dr., undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Moncure, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Monro, Dr., undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Moore, Jacob R. [invitation to the funeral of], 1837 December 9 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Moore, Dr. John [invitation to the funeral of], 1836 May 23 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Moore, Mary Anna [invitation to the funeral of], 1842 May 21 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Morelli, D. Gregorio, 1838 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - Morgan, Lady, 1845, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - Morrell, Mrs. and Miss, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - Murray, Catharine [invitation to the funeral of], 1832 October 29 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      - Mutter, Dr. and Mrs., undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
      - Naglee, Ellen [invitation to the funeral of], 1844 January 13 (Box 10, Folder 21)
      - Naglee, Mrs. Margaret [invitation to the funeral of], 1838 July 14 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      - Nancrede, Dr. and Mrs. J. G., 1840, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
      - Neill, Miss, 1823 January 29 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      - Newman, Mrs. J.S., undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
      - Nicklin, Mr. and Mrs. P.H., undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
      - Nicholas, Charles, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
      - Nixon, Mrs. and Misses, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
      - Norris, Dr. and Mrs., undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
      - Norris, Mr. and Mrs. C., undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
      - Norris, Mr. and Mrs. J., undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
      - Norris, Miss, undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
      - Norton, Mrs. Caroline, undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
      - Oakeley, George [invitation to the funeral of], 1835 December 15 (Box 10, Folder 34)
      - O'Connor, Miss, undated (Box 10, Folder 35)
      - Otis, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 10, Folder 36)
      - Otto, Dr. and Mrs., undated (Box 10, Folder 37)
      - Palmer, Mr. and Mrs., 1839, undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
      - Patterson, Mr., 1810 June 25 (Box 10, Folder 39)
      - Patterson, Eliza, undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
      - Patterson, R., 1837, undated (Box 10, Folder 41)
      - Pattison, Dr., 1835 December 25 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      - Peace, Dr. Edward, undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
      - Peck, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 10, Folder 44)
      - Pemberton, Mr., Mrs. and Miss, undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
      - Pepper, Mr. and Mrs. G. S., undated (Box 10, Folder 46)
      - Peries, Mr., undated (Box 10, Folder 47)
      - Perry, John George, 1845 July 11 (Box 10, Folder 48)
      - Peters, Francis, undated (Box 10, Folder 49)
      - Peters, R., 1837-1839, undated (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Peters, S.E., undated (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Peters, Miss, undated (Box 10, Folder 52)
      - Pettis, Mrs., 1841-1842 (Box 10, Folder 53)
      - Philadelphia Alms House, 1821 August 13 (Box 10, Folder 54)
      - Philadelphia Club, 1843 October 30 (Box 10, Folder 55)
      - Philadelphia Literary Circle, undated (Box 10, Folder 56)
      - Phillips, Mr. and Miss, undated (Box 10, Folder 57)
      - Physick, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 10, Folder 58)
      - Picot, Mr. and Mrs. Charles, 1841, undated (Box 10, Folder 59)
      - Pleasonton, Mr. and Mrs., 1840, undated (Box 10, Folder 60)
      - Pope, Mr., undated (Box 10, Folder 61)
      - Potts, Mrs. S.A., 1835 April 21 (Box 10, Folder 62)
      - Powel, Mr. S. and Mrs., 1840, undated (Box 10, Folder 63)
      - Preble, Commodore, 1806 August 1 (Box 10, Folder 64)
      - Quiblier, M., 1843 April 19 (Box 10, Folder 65)
      - Raquet, Mr., undated (Box 10, Folder 66)
      - Ralston, A.G., undated (Box 10, Folder 67)
      - Ralston, G., undated (Box 10, Folder 68)
      - Ralston, H., undated (Box 10, Folder 69)
      - Ralston, N., undated (Box 10, Folder 70)
      - Ralston, R., undated (Box 10, Folder 71)
      - Ralston, Miss, undated (Box 10, Folder 72)
      - Ramsay, Captain and Mrs., undated (Box 10, Folder 73)
      - Randall, A., 1841 October 25 (Box 10, Folder 74)
      - Randall, Mrs. J., 1839-1840 (Box 10, Folder 75)
      - Randolph, Dr. and Mrs., undated (Box 10, Folder 76)
      - Rawle, Mr., Mrs. and Misses, undated (Box 10, Folder 77)
      - Read, Captain and Mrs. George Campbell, undated (Box 10, Folder 78)
      - Read, Mr. and Mrs. J.M., undated (Box 10, Folder 79)
      - Read, Miss, undated (Box 10, Folder 80)
      - Redman, Miss, undated (Box 10, Folder 81)
      - Relf, Richard [invitation to the funeral of], 1836 September 26 (Box 10, Folder 82)
      - Relf, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 10, Folder 83)
      - Richards, Francis H., undated (Box 10, Folder 84)
      - Richardson, W.H., 1843 June 18 (Box 10, Folder 85)
      - Ricketts, Mr. and Mrs., 1839, undated (Box 10, Folder 86)
      - Ridgway, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 10, Folder 87)
      - Ritchie, Mary C., undated (Box 10, Folder 88)
      - Ritter, Charles Eugene and Francis Augustus [invitation to the funeral of], 1837 April 10 (Box 10, Folder 89)
      - Ritter, Jacob, Jr. [invitation to the funeral of], 1840 June 27 (Box 10, Folder 90)
      - Ritter, Susan [invitation to the funeral of], 1841 October 4 (Box 10, Folder 91)
      - Roberts, E.F., undated (Box 10, Folder 92)
      - Roberts, Mrs., undated (Box 10, Folder 93)
      - Robeson, Mrs. and Miss, undated (Box 10, Folder 94)
      - Robinson, G., undated (Box 10, Folder 95)
      - Robinson, Mrs. John, undated (Box 10, Folder 96)
      - Robinson, Minnie, undated (Box 10, Folder 97)
      - Robinson, Moore, undated (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Robinson, M., undated (Box 10, Folder 99)
      - Robinson, Wirt, undated (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Roebuck, J.N. and Dr. J. Robert Black, undated (Box 10, Folder 101)
      - Roesme, Baron and Madame de, 1840 April 21 (Box 10, Folder 102)
      - Rogers, James, undated (Box 10, Folder 103)
      - Rogers, Judge, undated (Box 10, Folder 104)
      - Ross, M., 1838 February 15 (Box 10, Folder 105)
      - Rotch, B.S., undated (Box 10, Folder 106)
      - Rowland, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 10, Folder 107)
      - Rush, Benjamin (nephew of James Rush), undated (Box 10, Folder 108)
      - Rush, Elizabeth [invitation to the funeral of], 1834 November 5 (Box 10, Folder 109)
      - Rush, E.F. [Elizabeth Fox], undated (Box 10, Folder 110)
      - Rush, Dr. and Mrs. James, 1800-1846 (Box 10, Folder 111)
      - Rush, J. Murray, undated (Box 10, Folder 112)
      - Rush, Mrs. S[amuel], undated (Box 10, Folder 113)
      - Rush, William, undated (Box 10, Folder 114)
      - Russell, Mr., undated (Box 10, Folder 115)
      - Sarmiento, Mrs. and Mrs. Craig, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Schott, Mr. and Mrs., undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Scott, Mr., Mrs. and Miss, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Scull, Miss, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Sears, Mrs., undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Sergeant, Mr., Mrs. and Misses, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Shaw, Fanny, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Sheaff, Miss, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Sigoinge, A., undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Simms, Mrs., undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Sitgreaves, Mrs., undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Smith, Honorable Charles [invitation to the funeral of], 1836 March 18 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Smith, Charles W., 1836, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Smith, G. Roberts, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Smith, G.W., undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Smith, J. Browne, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)